片名：杀手雅各布・马尔
Jacob!
雅各布
Hush yourself.
不用喊了
He's in the living room,
he's playing a game.
他在卧室玩电子游戏
Jacob.
雅各布
Jacob!
I'm going to need your help today, ok?
你今天要来帮我个忙 行吗
You're going to help me chop some wood.
帮我砍些木柴
Now.
现在
You've been inside all day,
watching this garbage.
你每天宅在家里 玩这些垃圾
It's time to get some fresh air.
So let's go.
应该要出去呼吸一下新鲜空气 走吧
Alright.
好了
I don't want to see you inside,
until you finish chopping all that wood.
我不想再看到你宅在家 去吧木柴都砍了
You got it?
听到了吗
I'll be back to check on you later.
过会儿我会回来检查
What the hell's wrong with that boy?
那孩子怎么了
There's nothing wrong with him!
他没怎么
Everyday...he says less and less.
每一天 他的话越来越少
I don't get it.
我不知道
Its getting to the point where I'm starting
to forget what his voice sounds like.
我都快忘了他的声音什么样了
That's a little bit dramatic
now, don't you think?
有点戏剧化 不是吗
Is it?
是吗
All he wants to do is
sit around the house,
他只想坐在家里
watch movies, and play
those damn video games.
看电影 玩游戏
Stopped playing sports.
Stopped going camping.
不去运动 不去野营
Stopped everything.
什么都不去干
Want am I supposed to think?
我该怎么想
That its a phase, and he'll grow out it.
就把这当作他成长过程中的一个小停顿
Yeah.
Maybe so.
好吧 也许吧
Trust me. He's just going through
an awkward place in his life.
相信我 这只是他青春期的小问题
Ok?
He's going to be fine.
好吗 他会好的
ARGH!
啊
Jacob?
雅各布
What are you doing up?
你怎么了
You all right son?
孩子你还好吗
Is anything wrong?
出了什么事
Jacob.
雅各布
Right, now right click on that.
对的 现在点击右键
Right click.
右键
Its right-
然后
Select copy.
选择复制
Copy? Its right below Cut.
复制 复制选项在剪切的下面
Perfect, now go to wherever
you want to put that.
好了 粘贴到你要的地方
I don't know, wherever, its your-
Sure, that's fine.
我不知道 就是贴到你想贴的地方
No.
不
No no no, you don't need that.
No sir you don't need that.
不不不 你不用那样 不 先生 你别
I promise you,
you don't need that.
我保证你不用那样
Dude, is it fucking five yet?
伙计 见鬼的 五点到了吗
I wish.
我想是的
I can't wait to get the
hell out of here today.
我真想快点离开这个鬼地方
I agree.
我同意
Uh, no, that's your-
Perfect...
哦 不 你 好吧
No sir. This guys a fucking moron!
不 先生 这家伙是个白痴
No sir. No no no, its there.
不 先生 不 不 不 我还在
Sure. Yes its right on top.
是的 它在右上角
No? Are you looking at the top?
不 你看到上面了吗
Ok.
好的
Why don't you look at the top
Now tell me what you see, at the top.
那你可以看一下上面 现在告诉我
你在上面看到了什么
Yeah, is that it?
Ok, now click that.
是的 看到了没 好的 点击一下
Un-fucking-believable!
Its like when I say look at the top,
真是不敢相信 我让他看一下上面
where is he looking
at the fucking ceiling?
他居然给我看天花板
No I don't see it. I don't see the
command. Anywhere.
不 我没有看到 我没有看到指令 哪儿都没
Nope.
没
Yeah, that's it. Just click that.
-Uh, sounds like you got it.
是的 就是它 点击一下
呃 你的问题解决了
Thank you for calling Darklight
Solutions, and have a great day.
感谢你致电夜光客服中心 祝你愉快
What are you girls
crying about over here?
你们刚才在这儿吐槽什么
What's the matter Rundy?
Heard there was a conversation
怎么了 伦迪 你听到什么吐槽了
you weren't a part of?
难道你没吐槽
I like to be involved.
-I'm sure.
好吧 我的确吐槽了
Can't wait to get the
fuck out of here today.
今天我真是不想再待在这儿了
Yeah you ain't kidding.
你别开玩笑了
Why do you want to leave?
Its not like you do any work.
你当然不会想离开 你又没什么事
Hey.
You wouldn't know it,
嘿 你不明白
but it takes a lot of work to do no
work and look like I do.
我做了很多事 只是看上去很闲
Its like a job, in and of itself.
但这本身就是一种工作
That almost makes sense.
你说得对
Does in my mind.
我是用脑子工作
So why are you in such a
rush to get out of here?
你为什么那么急着离开这儿
Well, more than usual anyway.
比平时还着急
Camping.
野营
Camping? It's fucking 20 degrees outside.
野营 户外20度
What camping?
什么野营
Rented a cabin for the weekend.
-Who did?
租了个小木屋度周末
有谁
Me, Dan, some friends.
我 丹以及一些朋友
That's not that place you usually
get up in New Hampshire is it?
不去你们一直去的新罕布什尔吗
No I-
-I swear. I swear its there.
对的 我
我发誓 我发誓就在那儿
Listen, you don't have a
different version of windows
听着 你和这个星球上其他人用的
than everybody else on the planet sir.
You don't. Trust me.
是一个版本的系统 相信我
No. I found this one
online, its way better.
不 我在网上找到的这处地方更好
Its out in the middle
of nowhere in Maine.
它在缅因州比较偏的地方
Hmm, sounds like a horror movie.
嗯 听上去像是恐怖片
Yeah, some guy from Boston bought
and fixed it up as a rental.
是的 一些波士顿的家伙买下了那里出租
Was it expensive?
那儿贵吗
No, actually we're the first ones
to rent it since he renovated,
不 事实上我们是那里的第一批租客
so we got a pretty good deal.
所以有优惠
That's it!
没错
I can't deal with these fucking
people anymore. We....
我受不了这些白痴了 我们
should get an early leave so we can
get ahead of the traffic.
应该早点出发避开高峰
I would.
我同意
Of course you would.
I'm somewhat responsible.
你当然同意 可我还有工作要做
Ah, you're crazy.
呃 你疯了
I mean, I supposed we could...
我认为 我们可以
Just in case.
以防万一
We do have to pick up Claire.
我们要去接克莱尔
Its true.
没错
Alright, fuck it.
Let's get out of here.
好了 管它呢 我们走吧
Have a good time, boys.
祝你们旅途愉快 兄弟
Well well well,
look at this pack of bitches.
啧啧啧 看看这群贱人
Wow.
-Jesus, what's up with that?
哇哦
天啊 怎么了
I know, its just not nice.
我觉得有点不妙
Alright, let's get this show on the road.
得了 上车再说
Why is she so mean?
她什么意思
I  think she has an imbalance.
我想她神经了吧
I'd buy that.
[KNOCKING]
我买的
Oh, can't get in?
噢 不进去吗
You got to unlock the door.
[LAUGHS]
你开一下门
Bitches.
贱人
So Ted, you never answered
my email about this place.
泰德 你给我的邮件没提到这个地方
Have you talked to that guy?
你跟别人提过吗
I talked to the owner, Bob, last week.
我上周和屋主鲍勃谈过
What did he say?
他怎么说
He said something about there
having been delays in the repairs.
他说那里的翻修因为一些事耽误了
Isn't that a problem?
有问题吗
He said he was going to go up there
to make sure this weekend was right,
他说他会去那里亲自翻修
and do the repairs himself.
确保周末一切顺利
Well, that's good.
那太好了
But, you haven't talked to him since?
但你之后没有和他联系过吗
No, I called him a
couple of days ago,
没有 我是几天前和他联系的
but I haven't heard back.
他没给我回电
Well, isn't that a problem?
I mean how are we going to get inside?
那有问题吗 我是说我们到时怎么进去呢
Oh ye of little faith.
别担心
He said he wasn't sure how long
the repairs were going to take,
他说过他不会在那儿翻修很久的
and cell service is crappy up there anyway,
so if we didn't hear from him,
那里信号太差 所以他才没回电吧
we should just head up there,
我们只管去
and he would leave the key
for us under the "pirate pig".
他会把要是放在海盗猪下面
The what?
那是什么
He said we'd know it when we saw it.
他说我们到了那儿就知道了
Nice security.
好吧
Its the country,
everybody trusts everybody.
那是乡下 夜不闭户
Isn't this guy, Bob, from Boston?
-Oh whatever.
那个鲍勃不是吧 他来自波士顿
没关系
I'm sure the repairs
just took longer than he thought.
我想翻修工作只是比他想的久了点
Its fine.
没事的
Hope so.
但愿如此
Me too.
我也是
Hey.
嘿
Have you spoken to Doug today?
-Yeah.
你今天和道格说过吗
说过
I talked to him earlier.
Why?
我之前和他说过 怎么了
So he's still coming then?
- Of course.
他过会儿会去吗 当然
Nice.
那就好
Where are we going to meet him?
我们在哪儿和他碰头
We're meeting him in the McDonalds
parking lot on 95 in Dedham.
我们和他在戴德姆95号大道的麦当劳停车场碰头
Cool.
很好
Hey so what's up with Dan and Doug?
丹和道格怎么了
What's that supposed to mean?
什么意思
You should have seen your face just now
when he said we were meeting Doug.
你应该看看他说我们要去见道格时 你脸上的表情
It lit up like a Christmas tree.
笑意盎然 容光焕发
I don't know what you
are talking about.
我不知道你在说什么
I just haven't seen him
in a while that's all.
我只是很久没见他了
You talk to him all the time in that game.
-Its not the same.
你在游戏里一直和他说话
那不一样
You know.
你懂的
Its ok. If you have a little
man-crush on Doug, you can say it.
好吧 你是不是对他有点男人间的欣赏
Its cool to be gay.
同性恋也挺酷的
Fuck off, I'm not gay.
闭嘴 我不是同性恋
No its all right. I've got a gay uncle.
Its totally cool.
好吧 我有一个同性恋的叔叔 挺酷的
I'm not gay.
我不是同性恋
I'm sure you're not.
我知道你不是
You just want to touch his peepee.
你只是想摸摸他的屁股
Fuck off both of you.
Look...
你们都给我闭嘴
I don't even like going in the locker room
when other men are changing.
我只是不喜欢在其他人换衣服的时候 待在更衣室
What?
什么
When other men are getting
changed in the locker room,
当别的男人在更衣室换衣服
I don't like going in.
我就不想进去
What do you do if you have
to change for the gym?
那当你在健身房要换衣服的时候
你会怎么做
I just wait until everybody leaves.
我会等到所有人都离开以后
Why?
为什么
Because they're always trying to have a
conversation with me,while they're getting undressed.
因为他们总喜欢在没穿衣服的时候 跟我聊天
-So what's wrong with that?
那又怎么了
There are few things
in this world,
这世界上再也没有比
more uncomfortable than a
conversation with a naked man.
与一个赤裸的男人聊天更糟糕的事了
Ok, I'll have to give you that one.
- See?
好吧 这算个理由
看见没
Its rough.
那太糟了
You're trying to listen to
what they're saying,
你可以把注意力放在他们说的话上
meanwhile you can't help but
look down at their
当你忍不住看他们下面的时候
dangling piece of meat bouncing
around inches in front of your face.
那几英寸的东西总在你眼前晃来晃去
Inches?
What are you doing in there?
几英寸  那你怎么做的
You know what I mean.
你懂我的意思
No, I don't,
and I don't think I want to know.
不 我不懂 我也不认为我想懂
You know that's funny.
I never have a problem with that.
那可真有意思 我从来不会觉得那算问题
Well that's because you can't
be on your knees at the time.
那是因为那东西不会撞你膝盖上
Son of a...
真是
You do realize that Ellie is
going to be here this weekend.
你别忘了艾莉周末要来这儿
Oh, no.
I didn't.
噢 不 我没忘
What?
Are you jealous of her?
怎么 你嫉妒她
No, I'm not jealous of
her, its just...
不 我没有嫉妒她 只不过
she sucks.
她太糟了
She's totally wrong for him.
她只会麻烦他
Unlike you.
不像你
No asshole,
its got nothing to do with me.
混蛋 跟我无关
You should see the
way she treats him.
你应该看看她是怎么对他的
He waits on her hand and foot,
and she doesn't appreciate it.
他把她照顾得无微不至 她却不懂感激
Not only that,
she has no sense of humor.
不仅如此 她还毫无幽默感
Well, I mean they've been
married for two years,
我觉得 他们已经结婚两年了
and they were
together for...what?
在此之前 他们已经
Three before that. Why do you
think he's still with her?
在一起三年了 你觉得他们为什么还在一起
That's exactly what I'm
trying to find out.
说实话我也不知道为什么
Well, all kidding aside,
好了 别开玩笑了
I think its cute that you have a
little nonsexual man-crush on him.
我觉得你对他那种男人间的欣赏挺逗的
I don't!
我没有
Its just...
只是
He's a lot of fun,
他很有趣
and I haven't gotten to hang out with him
really since he's gotten married.
自从他结婚 我已经不找他出去玩了
That's all.
就是那样
Sure, whatever works.
好吧 不管怎样
You're both assholes.
你们都是混蛋
Look...
听着
We've all known Doug for a lot of years,
我们已经认识道格很多年了
but you have not hung out
with her like I have.
但你们也从来不找她出去玩
Mark my words, Ellie can, and will,
suck the life out of this weekend.
相信我 艾莉只会毁了我们的周末
Where we meeting them again?
我们在哪里跟他们碰头
Just up ahead actually.
就在前面
We're going to follow them the
rest of the way to the cabin.
然后我们就跟着他们去木屋
And who's going to be there?
去那儿的都有谁
Ted, Dan, and Claire.
泰德 丹和克莱尔
Claire's going to be there?
克莱尔也要去
I thought you liked Claire?
我以为你喜欢克莱尔
You know what, its fine.
你知道什么 算了
It'll be fine. I'm sure we're not going
to hang out with them that much anyway.
反正不管怎样我们都要和她们一起去玩了
I can not wait to get outside and
check out gorgeous mountain trails,
我迫不及待地想看看美丽的山路
that I saw on that website.
就像我在网上看到的那样
Well, I mean...
Remember, it is a small cabin,
那个 记得吧 那只是个小木屋
we are going to hang out
with them at some point.
我们是和他们一起出去玩的
They just...
seem so much younger than you.
他们只是看起来比你年轻
Hey!
They're not that much younger than me.
嘿 他们没有比我年轻多少
Or, well, Dan isn't anyway.
反正丹没有
Besides, there's no age limit on friends.
再说了 交朋友年龄不是问题
I know. Ted's alright,
but Dan, I find creepy.
我明白 泰德没什么 但是丹 令人毛骨悚然
That's my oldest friend
you're talking about, you know.
他是他们里面年纪最大的
I can't help it.
He is always staring at me.
我受不了 他总是盯着我看
What?
I think he has a thing for me.
笑什么 我觉得他对我有想法
I think you're imagining things.
-Well...
我认为你想多了
可是
I don't think so.
我不那么认为
Look...
听着
I've been planning this
thing for a while,
我已经计划这件事很久了
and you promised that if you
came, you would be nice.
向我保证 你要跟他们好好相处
I'm always nice.
我很好相处的
I just...have my limits.
我只是有自己的底线
Yes you do.
是啦
Hey guys!
嘿 伙计们
What's up fellas?
你们好吗
Hello.
你们好
Yo, what's up sucka?
哟 你好
How you doing?
你们怎么了
I'm good.
You?
我很好
Wonderful.
-Glad to hear it.
你好
Hey slut.
嘿 小妞
Cock.
哥们
So you ladies ready for
some wilderness survival?
女士准备好野外生存了吗
You can keep the wilderness
survival, I'm ready for relaxation.
你去野外生存 我可是去度假的
You don't know what you're missing.
那你会错过很多的
I think I do.
- I'm down.
我还是要度假
我很乐意
That's what I'm talking about.
High five!
那就是我要说的 好兄弟
Claire?
克莱尔
I choose not bitter cold.
我选不受冻的那个
What?
Its not even that bad.
什么呀 没那么糟
Fire, warmth, and comfort....
火堆 温暖 舒适
These are things we've
achieved as a society.
这些是人类社会必需的
It was be foolish
to go backwards.
倒退才是愚蠢的
You guys are killing me!
你们这群家伙真是要命
Alright, let's get going.
好了 我们走吧
Its going to be late enough as
it is by the time we get there.
别在这儿磨蹭了 该走了
So...where we going?
那 我们要去哪儿
We're going up 95 until
we get to The Forks,
我们要沿着95号大道开到福克斯
then we're going to cross over to
Route 18 for about a half an hour,
然后是沿着18号公路一个半小时的车程
and then after that
its a small road I guess,
这之后 我猜还有条小路要开
a US Lyons road,
for another half a mile.
到US里昂路 又是半英里
Jesus, its certainly off the beaten path.
真是不走寻常路
You said you wanted secluded.
你说过你喜欢隐秘小路
True!
Alright, I love it .
没错 我喜欢
Let's go.
我们走吧
I know isn't that wild?
那没那么荒凉
You're making that up.
- I swear I'm not.
你在开玩笑
我发誓我没有
Where are we?
我们到哪儿了
We're a few hours into Maine.
We're about to hit 18.
我们已经在缅因州开了几个小时的车
大概快到18号公路
I'm hungry.
我饿了
Yeah, me too.
我也是
You hungry?
- No, but I'm thirsty.
你们饿了
我渴了
Alright, well, we're still
about an hour or so away,
好吧 我们至少还有一小时的路
so we should
probably stop here.
在这里停一会儿
Looks like there's a
convenience store up ahead.
看上去前面有家便利店
How's that?
- Good.
怎么样
好的
Is Doug still behind us?
道格还跟在我们后面吗
Yup.
是的
Can't you sense his presence?
你难道感受不到他的存在
I refuse to take part in your petty jibes.
我不想跟你抬杠
You want anything?
-No I'm good.
你要什么
不用了
Holy shit!
该死
What?
怎么了
What do you mean "what "?
Look at the name.
你说怎么了 看这个招牌
I don't understand, "Voorhees Market".
我不懂 沃里斯超市
So?
所以呢
So, the name "Voorhees"
means nothing to you?
所以 沃里斯对你没有意义吗
Should it?
应该有吗
Never mind.
没事了
Go ahead.
走吧
Hey.
嘿
You see the name on the store?
你看到这家店的店名吗
Yeah, we totally got to get a
picture of that before we go.
是的 我们走之前应该拍张照
I know, right?
我知道的
That's all I'm saying.
我就这么想的
What's up?
怎么了
Ellie sucks!
艾莉糟透了
Quit being a baby!
别那么幼稚
I'm not being a baby.
不是我幼稚
Now I shall go get some ice cream.
我去买一些冰淇淋
Sweet Christ,
they have pixie sticks.
太好了 他们有仙女棒
Get the fuck out.
真棒
They also have 24 foot licorice whips.
他们还有24英尺的甘草鞭
We've hit the mother load.
我的妈啊
What about the chocolate?
有巧克力吗
I didn't check.
我没看
You disgust me.
你真是的
There's much you've yet to learn.
Excuse me.
你还有得学 让一下
So, where you folks from?
你们从哪儿来
We just moved back to Mass, from New York.
我们刚从纽约来马斯
So then you're Red Sox fans.
所以你们是波士顿红袜的粉丝
You are aren't you?
- Yeah, definitely.
你们不是吗
是的 当然是
Thank God.
感谢上帝
Where you headed?
你们要去
Up to The Forks.
We got a cabin out there.
到福克斯 我们在那儿租了间小屋
That's nice.
真不错
Should be a beautiful weekend.
周末愉快
That'll be six bucks.
总共六美元
So, uh...
where abouts is this cabin?
那座小屋在哪儿
Excuse me?
什么
This cabin you rented.
Where is it?
你们租的小屋 在哪里
Its off of Route 18, US Lyons road.
它在18号公路尽头 US里昂路
You know it?
你知道它
I do.
我知道
Family came in here, on their
way out there, last week.
上周有一家人在去那儿的途中来过这里
Nice folks.
很不错的一家人
That must have been Bob, the owner.
The guy who fixed it up.
那应该是屋主鲍勃  他刚翻修了小屋
There was some delays
with the work,
那儿的翻修工作有延误
he went up there to finish it.
他自己去翻修了
Its a little light to call it a delay,
don't you think?
称之为延误有点太轻巧了 你说呢
I'm sorry, I don't understand.
Why, what would you call it?
不好意思 我不明白 你为什么那么说
I'd say some workers went missing.
There's your delay.
你所谓的延误 指的是一群工人的失踪
Missing?
失踪
They were there one moment,
gone the next.
他们一起去的 然后消失了
How do grown men, go missing?
一群成年男人 怎么会失踪
They're probably going off
into the woods to take a piss.
他们也许去树林里小便
Just got lost.
迷路了
Around here that can happen?
那里会发生这种事吗
These woods are tough to navigate,
even for us locals.
即使是当地人 也会在这片树林里迷路
Its tricky.
它挺棘手的
You get spun around,
and everything starts looking the same...
转一圈 周围一切看上去都一样
and the direction you thought
you were going in
你走的方向
turns out to be not the
direction you were going in.
不是你要去的方向
Its tough for us locals here,
but these guys were from out of state.
当地人都这样 别说那群外来的了
Its much harder for them.
对他们来说更难了
Did they ever find the guys?
他们后来被找到吗
Unfortunately, Miss, they didn't.
很不幸 小姐 他们没有
Keep that in mind.
记住
Don't go wandering too
far from the cabin.
别离开小屋太远
Unless there's a
trail or something.
除非有条路还是什么的
Alright?
好吗
We won't.
Thanks.
我们不会的 谢谢
Need a bag for this?
要袋子装吗
No, I'm good.
不用了
You folks have a good time.
祝你们愉快
I didn't mean to get
you upset or anything.
我不是故意要扫你们的兴
Sometimes I can't keep my trap shut.
有事我管不住自己的嘴
Its ok.
Have a good night
没关系 晚上好
Should be around here somewhere.
应该就在这儿附近
Wait, stop!
等一下 停车
What!
怎么了
There it is.
在那儿
Some co-pilot you are.
你是副驾驶
I wonder how far it is.
我想知道还有多远
This is amazing!
太神奇了
I can't believe how
secluded this place is.
我不敢相信这里居然这么隐蔽
Isn't it great?
太棒了
Pure nature.
纯天然
Its beautiful.
太美了
This is a nightmare.
- What?
真是场噩梦
怎么了
I've seen entirely too many horror
movies to be in a place like this.
我看过太多恐怖片都是这样的场景
Weren't you the one who-
你又不是
OH SHIT!
哦 见鬼
Shit.
见鬼
Well there's no damage
done to my car, so...
我的车没撞坏
no harm done.
一切平安
Other than this...
除此之外
OH SHIT ITS ALIVE!
哦 见鬼 它还活着
Jesus Christ!
-Its like a super deer!
上帝 它是头超级鹿
Maybe we should kill it.
也许我们该杀了它
Put it out of its misery.
解除它的痛苦
Go for it.
去做吧
Nice. Way to throw me under the bus.
你卖我卖得还真痛快
Seems fitting, seeing as though you're
the one who threw Bambi under the car.
你最合适 谁让小鹿斑比是你撞的
Good point.
这理由好
Well, what should we do?
我们该做什么
We could drag it off
to the side of the road,
我们要把它拖到路边
and let nature take its course.
尘归尘 土归土
What if we run over it again?
我们开车碾过去怎么样
I don’t want to get deer
bits stuck under my car.
我可不想再让鹿撞到我车下
You could beat it with a stick.
- You people are savages!
你可以用棍子打它
你们这群野蛮人
Grab its legs! Fucking grab it!
抓住它的腿 抓住
I can't stay with those people.
They are monsters!
我受不了那些家伙 他们是怪物
Listen, I understand what you are saying,
but they're good people.
听着 我能理解你说的 但他们是好人
Fuck, its just moved.
Shit, give me that tree branch!
见鬼 它动了
该死 给我那根树枝
Good people?
Good people don't do...this...
好人 好人会做这种
I know, its true, but...
我明白 但是
I know they're a little immature,
but they have good hearts.
我知道他们不太成熟 但他们很热心
That is when they're not trying to
他们不是故意要掌控
administer the death penalty to a deer.
那头鹿的生死
I don't know Doug.
我不知道 道格
Then trust me, because I do.
Alright?
那就相信我 好吗
Just give them a chance because
I think they will surprise you.
给他们一个机会 他们会给你一个惊喜的
[DAN] I think he just pissed on me!
他欺人太甚
[DAN] Give me that stick!
-I will do my best, for you.
给我棍子
我会为你尽力的
[TED] Fucking twist it. Twist it!
- That's all I ask.
打它 打它
那就对了
Ellie.
艾莉
Ellie, I'm...
so sorry about all that.
艾莉 我 很抱歉
We were able to...
我们已经
gently move the deer to the side of the
road where it quietly passed away.
把这头鹿轻轻地搬到路边 让它安息
We can go now if you
think you can go on.
如果你感觉好些了 我们现在就可以出发
Thanks Ted.
谢谢你泰德
I'll be ok.
我会好的
We can go.
我们走吧
Can little miss drama push on?
那女人的哭戏演完了吗
Dan.
丹
She'll be fine.
她没事了
Let's just go before
anything else happens.
快走吧 以免夜长梦多
Place looks good.
这地方看上去不错
Yeah it does.
没错
No kidding.
真棒
Ted, you've outdone yourself this time.
This is fantastic!
泰德干得好 这儿太棒了
It really is quite pretty, Ted.
这里真的太美了 泰德
Thank you.
谢谢
Honey, can you get the bags?
甜心 你能拿一下行李吗
Let's go in and check out
the place first,
我们先进去看看屋子的环境
then we can come back and get
the bags afterwards.
然后我们再来拿行李
That's fine by me,
I have to pee really bad.
我无所谓 我只是想上厕所
I don't want them to sit
in the cold too long.
我不想待在冰天雪地里太久
Doug, can you just get ours?
道格 那你就拿一下我们的行李好吗
Sure babe, I'll grab our stuff and
you guys can check out the door.
当然宝贝 我会提行李 你们去看一下环境
I'm going to grab my bags too.
我也要去拿我的包
Let's go pee.
我们去上厕所
Where did you say the key was again?
你之前说钥匙在哪儿来着
He said it would be under the pirate pig!
他说钥匙在海盗猪下面
Oh, right...
哦 好的
Its not there, man!
它不在这儿
I'm not blind, dude.
我又不瞎 兄弟
Fuck.
见鬼
Claire, will you check around.
克莱尔 在周围找找
Ted, there's nothing over here!
泰德 这里什么都没
Fuck!
见鬼
He said he'd hide it
under the "pirate pig"?
他说过他藏在海盗猪下面的
Yeah.
是的
Oh, alright.
哦 好吧
Well maybe he forgot
and hid it somewhere else.
也许他忘了藏到哪里去了
Give him a call and find out.
打他电话找钥匙
No service.
Anyone else?
没有信号 谁有信号
[CLAIRE] Nope.
没
Nothing.
Yeah, nothing here.
好吧 这儿没信号
Great.
见鬼
Alright, well...
好吧
I'll head back down to the main road until
I get a signal and I'll give him a call.
我到主干道上去找信号 再给他打电话
Dude, did you try the door?
兄弟 你怎么不试着开开门
Why would I try the door?
为什么我要试着开门
Ah, my hero!
啊 英雄
After you...
你先进
You're the man.
你真棒
Nicely done.
-I am "the man".
干得好
我真棒
So I hear.
我听到了
Wow, this place really is awesome.
Did you know it was this well setup?
这地方太棒了 你之前就知道这儿这么棒吗
No, I didn't.
不 我没想到
I love the feel of it. You know?
我喜欢这个风格
Its very welcoming.
Very warm and lived in.
这里既温暖又合适居住
Yeah.
是的
I wonder how much work went
into the restoration process.
我想翻修工作一定花了不少心血
Well, this is why the
door was unlocked.
我知道门为什么没锁了
What's that?
什么
Looks like someone snapped
the key off, in the lock.
有人把钥匙断在门锁里了
That's odd.
真怪
Yeah, tell me about it.
I'm surprised Bob didn't mention that.
我很奇怪 鲍勃怎么没提过
Better?
怎么样
Better, um...
好多了
We are the only ones who are supposed
to be here this weekend, right?
我们是周末唯一租了这屋子的人 是吗
Yeah, why?
是的 怎么了
There's a whole set of
toiletries in the bathroom.
浴室有一整套的洗漱用品
Really?
-Yeah.
真的吗
是的
Toothpaste, toothbrush, deodorant
soap, the whole nine yards.
牙膏 牙刷 除臭皂 应有尽有
Kitchen's fully stocked too.
厨房的食材也充足
Stocked with what?
有什么
Everything.
Like Kitchen Stadium everything.
什么都有 和美食节目的厨房一样
What kind of deal did
this guy give you?
租房子还附赠这些吗
I don't know.
我不知道
I mean, did you blow
him or something?
你是威胁了屋主还是怎样
Douglas!
道格拉斯
I didn't do anything to warrant this.
我从来没要求过这些
You are sure we're the only ones who
are supposed to be here, right?
你确定就我们租了这里吗
Yeah, I checked multiple times.
是的 我反复确认过
We are the only people
here this weekend.
我们是这周末唯一的租客
Maybe its a thank you?
For putting up with the delays,
也许这是之前返修延误的
and the repairs and everything?
补偿之类的
I guess that's possible...
我觉得有可能
Can you check upstairs?
你看过楼上吗
Yeah, sure.
是的 当然
What are you thinking?
你在想什么
I don't know, but this
is definitely weird.
不知道 只是有点古怪
What? I'm hungry!
看什么 我饿了
There's clothes in all of the
drawers in the room upstairs.
楼上的衣柜里都是衣服
Shit!
见鬼
What the fuck?
I'm going to kill Bob!
该死的 我要杀了鲍勃
We drove all the way up
here for nothing?
我们大老远开车来这儿干嘛
Maybe we should leave.
也许我们该离开
That's ridiculous,
where we going to go?
太荒谬了 我们能去哪儿
Yeah, fuck that! I put down way
too much money on this place.
是的 该死 我为了这里花了不少钱
Look, let's not get ahead
of ourselves, alright?
听着 我们准备不足
What time is it?
几点了
10 o' clock
十点
Alright, its 10 o'clock
now and no one's here.
好吧 都十点了 这儿还没人
If someone was
staying at the cabin,
也许小屋有人
where else would they be?
可他们能在哪儿呢
We had a long drive, none of us
are going to bed anytime soon.
我们开了那么久的车 现在都需要马上休息
Let's just enjoy the rest
of the evening,
我们就好好享受今晚余下的时光
pretend like nothing's wrong. If someone
shows up, we explain what happened,
就当什么都没发生 等别人来了我们再解释
if not, we figure it out in the morning.
如果没人出现 我们明天再去弄清楚
Sound good?
怎么样
I'm good.
我同意
Sounds good.
好的
Yeah?
怎样
Sure, why not?
当然 就这样吧
Great, alright.
好吧
Let's get our stuff up into our rooms,
come back down and shake this off.
那我们先进房间 把这些行李放好
Hey, don't worry.
Once we get settled I'll make some drinks,
嘿 别担心 等安顿好了喝几杯
and then you can't help
but have a good time.
你肯定能玩得开心
Ok, I could sure use
a good time.
好吧 我想我们会开心的
You know what?
This is absurd.
你们知道吗 这太荒谬了
Its midnight.
No one's coming.
都半夜了 没人来
Are we going to waste our weekend
because of a couple of toothbrushes?
难道为了几只牙刷 浪费我们的周末吗
Fuck that!
见鬼
Let's play some cards.
我们玩牌吧
Fuck yeah!
I'm in.
没错 我玩
I'll make fresh drinks.
我去倒几杯酒
You in, buddy?
你玩吗 兄弟
Ummm, no we're going
to call it a night.
嗯 我们准备休息了
We're getting up early
to go hiking tomorrow.
明天我们还要早起徒步旅行
I'll be up in a second.
我一会儿去
晚安 大家
晚安
You sir, are a dildo.
-What do you want me to say,
你真是个妻管严
你想让我说什么
I'm tired.
我累了
We'll hang out tomorrow night.
-Whatever.
我们明晚还要出去
不管如何
Do you want to come
hiking with us?
你想和我们一起去徒步吗
Well, what time are
you getting up?
好吧 你们几点起床
I don't know, 7-
我不清楚 七
Nope, I'll pass.
-Ok, well there it is.
不 我不去了
好吧 就这样
I'll see you tomorrow.
明天见
Good night guys!
晚安 大家
See you tomorrow.
明天见
Are you in?
你玩吗
Or do you want to update your diary about
everything Doug said to you today?
还是你要写日记 记下今天道格和你说的话
Deal the cards, you asshole!
玩牌 混蛋
Whoa, easy there tiger.
Welcome back to the land of the living.
哇哦 放轻松 你总算醒了
Hey, listen, you need to really take
it easy with those whiskey-
嘿 你真的要少喝点威士忌
Whose car is that out there?
-What?
外面的车是谁的
什么
I don't know,
it was here when we got up.
我不知道 我醒来它就在那儿了
And you didn't see anybody with it?
你没有看到开车的人吗
No.
But Claire got up before I did.
没有 不过克莱尔起得比我早
Yeah but there wasn't
anybody around that I saw.
我没看到附近有什么人
I tried to check whose it was,
but it was locked...
我想看看这是谁的 但是它锁着
and the tires are flat...
轮胎也是瘪的
Perfect.
好吧
Do you think it could have
been there last night?
你说这是不是昨晚开来的
Maybe.
也许吧
I mean, it is kind of tucked away.
我觉得它比较隐蔽
Have you guys seen Doug and Ellie?
你们看到道格和艾莉了吗
Yeah, they went for a hike.
是的 他们去徒步了
Oh yeah, that's right.
哦 对了 好吧
You know what?
你知道什么
Maybe you should go down
to the main road.
也许你应该去主干道
See if you can call Bob,
and get some answers.
给鲍勃打电话问问情况
Yeah, that's not a bad idea.
这主意不坏
Alright, well, I think I'm going
to shower and clean up a bit.
好吧 我要去洗澡清理一下
I still feel a little...foggy.
我还是觉得有点 糊涂
And then I'll head back
to the road until I get a signal.
然后我会去主干道看看 能不能有信号
Do you want to come?
-No thanks.
你想跟着吗
不 谢谢
I'm going to
check out the basement.
我去看看地下室
It looks really
creepy down there.
那儿真有点毛骨悚然
Ok, that's weird.
Will you move Doug's car for me?
好吧 有点怪 你能帮我移一下道格的车吗
Yeah, we can swap it when
you get out of the shower.
等你洗完澡 我们交换
Dan, you want to come?
-No, I'm cool.
丹 你要来吗
不 我不要
I'm going to go back outside.
Grab a beer, walk around.
我要到外面去 拿瓶啤酒 随便走走
Well, I'm glad I could be of
service to the two of you.
我很高兴为你们两个服务
No problem.
没问题
Oh hey, do you know where my bags are?
哦 嘿 你们知道我的包在哪儿吗
Yes, you left them down here, so we
threw them in the room upstairs.
知道 你昨天丢在这儿 所以我们把它们放到楼上房间了
That reminds me.
这倒提醒我了
How come you get the big bed upstairs
in the room with Doug and Ellie,
你为什么把楼上大床房给了道格和艾莉
and we get the
little bunk beds down here?
把楼下的小铺位给我们
Look, if you want to listen to
Doug and Ellie make out all night,
听着 如果你想听道格和艾莉的墙角
then feel free to-
那随意
Oh wait, you probably do.
噢 等等 你真的会这么做
Oh, cause of the gay thing again.
哦 你又提同性恋的事情了
Yeah that's funny.
是啊 那很有意思
Yeah! I want to fuck Doug in the mouth!
对的 我就是想上道格了行了吧
I want to wear him like a hat!
Its going to be great!
我想把他当帽子戴 那真有趣
No, that's me! You got me! I'm gay!
哦 那就是 你知道了 我是同性恋
I'm going to go outside and do other
gay things right now.
我现在就出去 干点同性恋干的事
Dan...
- Buddy!
丹
兄弟
I think you hurt his feelings.
你让他伤心了
I might have pushed that a little too far.
我玩笑开过分了
Maybe just a bit.
是有点过分
Ah well, he's like the
guy from Momento,
还好 他不记仇
he'll forgot about it in two minutes.
-True
没两分钟他就会忘记
没错
Later.
过会见
Yup.
好
How you doing back there?
回到那儿你会怎样
Great.
好的
Isn't it gorgeous?
很棒不是吗
Yup.
是的
Baby? What happened?
宝贝 怎么了
Its ok, keep going. I'll catch up.
没事 你继续 我会跟上的
I'm sorry.
Why didn't you tell me to slow down?
抱歉 我可以慢点走的
I'm fine, really.
我没事 真的
Its been a little while, huh?
你已经这样有一段时间了
A little more than I thought, I guess.
大概是很长一段时间了
I'm good though.
I just need to catch a second wind.
我还行 我只是需要喘个气
Come on, don't be silly.
We'll take a break.
得了 别傻了 我们休息一会儿
Well...
好吧
if you insist.
如果你坚持
I'm sorry honey,
I don't know what happened.
很抱歉 甜心 我不知道会这样
I guess all those hours
at the office lately,
我想是最近在办公室待久了
instead of on the
treadmill have cost me.
很少去跑步的缘故
Now now, I know hard
you've been working lately,
我知道你最近一直工作
and I know how tough
its been for you.
也知道对你来说很辛苦
That's why I wanted this
weekend for you so badly.
这就是我让你度周末的原因
Get you out of the office,
let you relax a little bit.
走出办公室 放松一下
I know you need it.
我知道你需要
Yeah but...
是的 但
I get that.
I just don't want to hold you up.
我知道 我只是不想阻碍你
Hush! You aren't holding me up.
I'm out here to be with you silly.
哦 你没有阻碍我 我正和你一起呢
But still...
但是
But nothing, we're almost
back to the cabin,
没有但是 我们快回到小屋了
we will take our time from here on out.
从现在起 我们要抓紧时间
Alright, but I still feel bad.
好 但我感觉还是有点糟
Please, it isn't a big deal!
拜托 那没什么大不了的
You really think I married
you for your six pack?
你真以为我是为了你的六块腹肌跟你结婚的
Well!
Seeing as though its more like a 1.5 pack,
现在只有一块半了
I can only assume its
because I have a big-
我能撑的起 因为我有个大
Hey what's that?
嘿 那是什么
What?
什么
That over there.
在那儿
That's strange, what is it?
Is that a nest?
真怪 那是什么 是个鸟巢吗
No, its too big for a nest.
不 比鸟巢大
Let's take a look.
去看看
What is it?
它是什么
Looks like a treehouse.
Something we'd build as kids.
像间书屋 我们小时候会建的那种
Who do you think made it out here?
谁在这儿建了它
I don't know.
Could have been here for centuries.
我不知道 我没来过
Or some children could have
built last week on vacation.
也许是放假的孩子们上周建的
Be serious.
真厉害
You know, it actually looks
pretty well crafted.
你懂的 它看上去像是精心建造的
Yeah, you're right.
Its very well supported.
是的 你说得对 它建造得很不错
Somebody put a lot
of time in on this.
有人花了很多时间在它上面
Want to climb up?
想爬上去吗
No...I don't think so.
不 我不想
Its kind of creepy.
有点毛骨悚然
Yeah. It is kind of creepy.
是的 是有点毛骨悚然
Especially considering the kind of
person who would want to live out here.
特别是想到谁可能住在这儿
Let's go Doug.
走吧 道格
Yeah, you're right.
好的 你说得对
We should get back anyway.
It will be dark soon.
我们快回去吧 天快黑了
Besides-
除了
Hey buddy!
Any luck?
嘿 兄弟 怎么样
Nope.
Went right to voicemail.
不行
一直是语音信箱
Anybody show up here?
-No.
有人来吗
没有
Its been really quiet actually.
很安静
You see the tires on that car?
你看见那车的轮胎吗
I told you, they're flat.
我告诉过你 它们瘪了
They're not just flat,
those are ripped apart.
不只是瘪 是撕裂的
What do you think
could have done that?
你认为是什么造成的
I don't know.
我不知道
Its too messy to be a knife puncture but...
很像是乱刀刺穿的 但是
I can't imagine all four
tires blowing out at once.
我很难想象四个轮胎一起爆
I got to say man, things are
really starting to pile up.
感觉怪事越来越多
I'm sure there's a reasonable
explanation for all of this stuff.
万事都有解释
Like what?
比如呢
I mean...
我的意思是
I guess the car could be Bob's,
我猜车可能是鲍勃的
maybe they couldn't find a place
to fix the tires,
他们可能没找到修轮胎的地方
so they left it here?
所以他们把车留在这儿
See?
这不就得了
Yeah but then how did he get home?
是的 但他们是怎么回去的
Maybe they brought a spare car?
也许他们还有一辆备用车
Who brings a spare car anywhere?
Its not like a toothbrush!
谁会到哪儿都带着备用车
又不是牙刷
Six Flags, two years ago. We brought a
spare car in case any of us got lucky.
两年前 六旗游乐园
我们就带了备用车以防我们走运
That way we wouldn't have to have
that awkward ride home conversation.
避免了我们骑车回家的尴尬
Alright that was your idea,
I didn't want to do it.
那是你认为的 我没那么想
Who thinks they are going to get
lucky at an amusement park?
谁会想到在一个游乐场里能那么幸运
Its the best time.
真是好时光
They're all off guard, its perfect.
她们措手不及 完美
Its amazing you're still single.
最惊人的是 你居然还单身
I don't like to be tied down.
我不想被绑住
No encumbrances...
无儿女的拖累
I'm sure that's it.
确实
Hey is Claire still in the basement?
嘿 克莱尔还在地下室吗
Yeah.
是的
What's going on with that anyway?
这到底怎么回事
What do you mean?
什么意思
Don't play games with me, buttercup,
you know exactly what I mean.
别耍我 你知道我在说什么
You two have been
awfully chatty lately.
你俩最近话不少
You're imagining things.
We're always chatty.
你瞎想什么 我们一直很多话
No! On the ride up here you
two were like Amos and Andy,
不 在来这儿的路上
你们就像是先知安迪
though neither of you were black.
虽然你们都不是黑人
First off, those guys are...
首先 那些家伙是
guys.
你懂的
Second of all...we're the
same we've always been.
第二 我们一直如此
You really going to throw
this company line at me?
你真的要用场面话堵我
Tell me you never thought
about getting with her.
别告诉我你没想和她在一起过
Ok, well, admittedly...
哦 好吧 我不否认
I have thought about it
from time to time, but...
我有时考虑过 但
we've been friends for what now?
Seven years?
我们当了多久的朋友 七年
I'm not sure I'm ready to be
in a long term relationship,
我不确定 如果我们在一起了
which is what it would
be if we got together.
能否维持比友谊更长久的感情
It wouldn't have to be.
想多了
Oh please...
哦 得了
Long term friends don't just hook up.
长时间的友谊并不容易
The "getting to know you"
phase is over,
认识你 这一阶段结束
and when that happens,
you're in it for the long haul.
你会发现 这才只是漫漫长路的开始
Besides...
除非
Getting together for the purely physical
would totally wreck the friendship.
在一起只是为了肉欲 不然会伤害友谊
I can't have that.
我不想那样
I won't.
我不会的
She turned you down, didn't she?
她拒绝你了吗
Yeah and she was totally
mean about it too!
是的 但她就是那么想的
What did she say?
她说了什么
I don't know. Something about
some guy she likes at work.
不知道 有时会说她在工作上喜欢的人
There's nothing you
can do about that.
你拿她没办法
I guess not.
我猜不是
You know what the worst part is?
你知道最糟的是什么
Is that I know the guy.
I mean, I don't "know" him,
是我知道那家伙
我的意思是 我虽然不认识他
but I know the guy
she talking about.
但我知道她说的那家伙
So what?
什么
He's got a mustache...
他留着胡子
You mean like a goatee?
山羊胡吗
Like a Fu Manchu?
傅满洲那样的吗
Like,a...beard, like...a...a chinstrap?
络腮胡吗 连着鬓角的胡子吗
Nope.
不是
Mustache...
八字胡
You got passed over for
a guy with a justasche?
你输给了一个八字胡吗
Yup!
Not exactly a shining moment.
是的 虽然不愿承认
That had to bum you off.
那样的打败了你
Dude, fuck her!
兄弟 上了她
Seriously.
真的
I mean... I love Claire like a sister,
she's awesome,
我是说 我把克莱尔当姐妹 她极好
but if she can't see all this?
Fuck her!
但是如果她拎不清 上了她
Thank you Dr Drew.
谢谢你 德鲁博士
That's what I'm here for.
那就是为什么我来这儿
Now if only I could
be as happy as you are,
如果我能像你一样快乐
beating off to internet porn with
a vibrator strapped to my nuts.
克制住肉体的欲望
I'd have the zen like existence you have.
像你一样苦修
Amen.
阿门
Holy fuck woman!
该死的女人
You trying to scare the
shit right out of me?
你想吓死我吗
Sorry. I was downstairs
looking at some old photos.
抱歉 我刚才在楼下看到些旧照片
Kind of freaked me out a little bit.
有点吓到了
Well, didn't you go down
there because it was freaky?
你不就是想找刺激下楼的吗
Yes.
是的
Whatever, what did you find?
算了 你发现了什么
Just some old stuff from the family
that apparently used to live here.
以前住在这里的一家人的旧东西
Like what?
比如
Furniture...
家具
old photos.  Stuff like that.
老照片之类的
I'm not sure why its still
down there but, its creepy.
我不明白为什么这些还在楼下
但是有点吓人
I don't know.
我不知道
The place was empty for
years before Bob bought it.
这地方空置了很多年
直到鲍勃买下了它
Were you or Dan hanging
around outside the basement?
是你还是丹刚才在地下室附近转悠
Huh?
哈
No.
I mean...
没有
We were out on the porch just
checking out the view, why?
我们刚才在走廊上 怎么了
Well then what are you doing here?
那你后来来这儿干什么
Came in to get another beer...
进来再拿点啤酒
Why?
怎么了
Nothing...
没事
Speaking of Bob, any luck?
说到鲍勃 有什么好消息
Nope.
没
Shit!
见鬼
Doug and Ellie aren't back yet?
道格和艾莉还没回来吗
No.
没
But I bet Ellie's going to keep
Doug away for as long as possible.
我打赌艾莉想带着道格离我们远远地
Dan will be upset.
丹会不高兴的
I know.
我懂
You coming outside?
你出来吗
Sure, I'll join you.
好 我会加入你们
Ok, will you grab us a
beer when you come?
好的 来的时候拿瓶酒
I thought you came in to do that?
我以为你进来就是拿酒的
Yeah but you're so much
closer to the fridge.
是的 但你离冰箱近
Ugh...fine!
Bunch of babies!
噢 好吧 懒鬼
I'm getting a little worried that
Doug and Ellie aren't back yet.
我有点担心 道格和艾莉还没回来
I'm sure they're fine.
他们没事的
Yeah they probably just got caught
up in all the beauty that is nature.
也许是他们沉醉于大自然的美景了
I guess so....
也许吧
I just saw something outside!
我刚才看到外面有东西
Like the darkness?
-No, asshole!
像是黑影
不 混蛋
I just saw someone or something outside!
我真的看到有什么人或什么东西在外面
Ok, which was it?
Are we talking about a person or animal?
哦 那是什么呢 是一个人还是动物
A person...I think.
一个人 我想
Once again, I have seen entirely too many
horror films to go down this road.
再说一次 我已经看了很多这种套路的恐怖片
So if you could stop talking like this, it
would really help in not freaking me out.
如果你们还要讨论下去
我吓得会受不了的
I'm not kidding.
我不是开玩笑
Well, maybe it was Doug or Ellie
coming back from their hike.
也许是道格或者艾莉徒步回来了
It didn't look like Doug or Ellie.
不像是道格或者艾莉
Alright, then what did it look like?
好吧 那他像什么
I don't know!
-Wh-
我不知道
I just saw movement out the kitchen window.
我只是在厨房窗户看到了影子
It could have been anything.
可能是任何东西
Ok, well if its "anything",
then go check it out.
好吧 那就再去看看那个任何东西
Fuck that!
该死
Oh yeah, I agree. Fuck that!
哦 我同意 该死
I don't care how silly it sounds, I'm
not going to be the "curious" one.
我不管那听起来有多傻
我不想成为那个好奇的人
If there's something
out there it can knock,
如果有什么在外面 它会敲门
otherwise I'm not going out there.
-I'm cool with that.
我可不想出去
我没兴趣
Its probably just an animal.
It will go away.
也许就是个动物 它可能走了
Fuck.
见鬼
Ok.
好吧
But if I'm going,
you're coming with me.
但如果我出去 你们也要跟着
Well that's done...
好吧
Fuck.
见鬼
Who the fuck is that!
那是谁
I don't know, but she's a fucking mess!
我不知道 但她看起来糟透了
Dan, help me get her on the couch!
丹 帮我把她抬上沙发
This isn't her blood.
这不是她的血
The hell it isn't!
Look at me!
见鬼的不是 看看我
No, it isn't hers.
不 不是她的
I don't know whose it is, but its not hers.
我不知道这是谁的血 但不是她的
[TED]
She's covered.
她穿着衣服
I know.
我知道
She has cuts, yes.
Bruises,yes, but that's it!
她有伤口 是的 淤伤 但没有血
With the amount of blood that's on her
clothes, it can't be hers.
看她衣服上的血量 不可能是她的
Honey, can you hear me?
Wake up!
甜心 你听得到吗 醒一醒
Honey, wake up!
Can you hear me?
甜心 醒一醒 听得到吗
What happened to you?
你发生了什么
She's out.
她在外面
Dan!
Go get me a tee shirt!
丹 去给我一件T恤
Dan, go!
丹 去啊
Help me turn her over?
帮我把她转过来
What the fuck is that?
那是什么
Looks like strap marks.
看上去是带状痕迹
Jesus.
天啊
What happened to this girl?
这女孩发生了什么事
I don't know.
我不知道
Can you get me some hot water?
能帮我拿杯热水吗
Yeah, sure.
好的
Did she say anything?
她说了什么
No.
Dan, get out of the light!
没有 挡着光了
Dan, if you're going
to be sick, get out.
丹 如果你受不了 可以出去
I'm going to be fine.
我没事的
Come on...
走吧
Well...I changed her
clothes but,
好吧 我给她换了衣服 但是
there still isn't anything
to lead to that much blood.
没有会流那么多血的伤口
She's still out I take it?
她还在外面吗
Yeah.
是的
Where the hell did she come from?
她从哪儿来的
Wherever she came from,
it knocked her out cold.
不管从哪儿来 她肯定是遇到麻烦了
Where are Doug and Ellie?
道格和艾莉在哪儿
Good question.
好问题
Now I'm really beginning to worry.
现在我真的开始担心了
I think we should go for help.
我想我们需要帮助
We can't leave without them.
我们不能把他们留在这儿
We don't know where they are, or
when they're coming back.
我们不知道他们在哪儿
也不知道他们什么时候回来
Meanwhile, we have a girl in the living
room who's covered in blood!
同时 我们还碰上这个浑身是血的女孩
Something happened to
her, we need to get help.
她遇到了什么事 我们要帮她
On the way here do you remember
seeing anything open this late?
来这儿的路上你记得有什么地方
开放到那么晚
All we have to do is find a house,
bang on the door,
我们要做的就是找个屋子 关上门
and get a
hard line to the cops.
然后报警
When was the last house you saw?
还记得你看到最近的屋子
是什么时候的事了
We should just wait for
Doug and Ellie to get back.
我们应该等道格和艾莉回来
Why? We're going to be in the
same situation we are now.
为什么 那和现在有什么区别
Yeah but then at least
we'll all be together.
是的 但至少我们在一起
We won't have to worry about
leaving people behind.
我们不用担心被我们丢下的人
We aren't leaving anybody behind!
We can leave a note or something.
我们没有把谁丢下 我们可以留张字条
The bottom line is...she needs help.
现在最重要的是 她需要帮助
Why do we have to leave right now?!
为什么我们一定要立刻离开
Claire said the blood isn't even hers!
克莱尔说血不是她的
I don't know, you saw
her, what do you think?
我不知道 你看过她了 你怎么想
I don't want to leave
Doug and Ellie either,
我也不想丢下道格和艾莉
and true, she doesn't seem
to be in any physical danger,
而且她的确看上去不像是有重伤
but she’s obviously been through
something traumatic, and she needs help!
但她明显是受伤了 她需要帮助
If we knew when they were coming back,
I'd say wait but...since we don't...
如果我们知道他们什么时候回来
我会等等 但是我们不知道
Of course you would agree with him.
当然你总是帮他的
What is that supposed to mean?
-Nothing.
什么意思
没什么
Look, if you feel that strongly about it,
stay here while I take her and go get help.
听着 如果你坚持待在这儿
我带着她去寻找帮助
I don't like that idea either,
we shouldn't split up!
我也不喜欢这个办法 我们不该分开
Alright well you can't
have it both ways.
我们不能两全其美
She needs help, I'm going
to take her to get it.
她需要帮助 我带她去求助
Stay here if you want.
如果你想 你就待在这儿
Claire?
克莱尔
Ok.
好的
I'll go with you.
我和你一起
Dan?
丹
Fuck...
该死
I can't stay here alone, I'll go.
我不能一个人待在这儿 我也去
Alright.
I'm going to go get the car started.
好吧 我去开车
Shit!
见鬼
Ted help!
[DAN] Ellie, thank god!
泰德 救命
艾莉 感谢上帝
I'm glad you guys are
back, but we have to go.
我很高兴你们回来了 但我们要走了
No, we have to get Doug!
- What happened?
不 我们要去找道格
发什么什么事
I had to run! I had to run,
Ted, but we have to go back!
我只能跑 我只能跑
泰德 但我们要回去
What are you talking about?
[DAN] Where the fuck is Doug?!
你在说什么
道格在哪儿
We were attacked in the woods.
- By who?
我们在森林里遭到袭击
谁干的
I don't know!
It all happened so fast!
我不知道
发生得太快了
There was so much blood....I...I
panicked, but we have to go back.
好多血 我 我害怕 但我们一定要回去
He could still be alive!
他可能还活着
[DAN] Alive!?
- Holy shit!
活着
该死
We need to get the fuck out of here!
-No, no we have to go back!
我们要离开这儿
不 不 我们要回去
We will, but first we need to get help.
Hold her, I'm going to start the car.
我们会的 但我们先要寻求帮助
抱着她 我去开车
Ellie, where's Doug?
Where did you leave him?
艾莉 道格在哪儿
你把他丢在哪儿了
Who's that?
那是谁
Ellie, you have to
tell us where Doug is.
艾莉 你要告诉我们道格在哪儿
No, no, no...
不 不 不
Ted!
What is going on?
泰德 发生了什么
Get inside and close the door!
进去 关门
We have to go.
我们一定要去
Just get inside!
快进去
What are we going to do?
我们要做什么
I don't know.
But the tires on both our cars are fucked.
我不知道 但是我们的车胎都爆了
What!?
什么
Yup. Just like the other car.
We aren't going anywhere!
是的 就像另一辆车那样 我们哪儿都去不了
Fuck that! We have to go after Doug!
该死 我们要去找道格
I don't know, maybe we
should wait until morning.
我不知道 也许我们应该等到明早
Are you kidding me?
你开什么玩笑
You heard what she said.
He could be hurt, who knows how badly!
你听到她说的了
他可能受伤了 鬼知道多严重
We don't know who's doing this,
fuck going outside right now!
我们不知道是谁干的 不能现在出门
I have to go after him, Ted.
我一定要去找他 泰德
I panicked before but I
can't leave him out there.
我之前是害怕 但是我不能把他留在那里
I have to go.
我要去
[DAN]
If someone's going to go, we should all go.
如果一个人要去 我们都去
I'm not going.
我不要
We have to go after him, Ted!
We weren't attacked too far from here!
我们一定要去找他 泰德
我们遇袭的地方离这儿不远
Please!
Please say that you will go after him!
拜托 请你们去找他
Fine!
I'll go by myself!
好吧 我自己去
[DAN] Wait, I'll go with you!
-Come if you want, but I'm going!
等等 我和你一起
如果你要去你跟上 我是要去的
Do you want to come?
你要一起吗
I do, but if she wakes
up I want to be here.
我会的 但在她醒之前 我留在这儿
All we found was this, snow, and
a whole lot of fucking blood!
我们发现的所有就是这个 雪 以及一大片血
What the fuck is going on?
会发生什么
I mean, what could have happened to him?
我是说 他会发生什么
I don't know.
我不知道
I think some kind of
fucking animal got him!
我想是某种动物袭击了他
Well, what else could have happened?!
那 还会发生什么
I don't know!
我不知道
She knows something.
她知道
Who the fuck is she?
她到底是谁
Everything started when she got here!
所有事都是她来这儿后发生的
[WHISPERED]
Hey!
嘿
Lower your fucking voices!
What is wrong with you?
小声点 你怎么了
I'm sorry, but we need to
figure out what to do.
抱歉 但我们要想想我们要做什么
I think we should all go look for Doug.
我想我们应该都去找道格
Ok.
Let's go.
好吧 走
I'm not going.
我不去
[CLAIRE]
What?!
什么
Ted, we need to get help.
泰德 我们需要帮助
Not this way, not now.
不是这种方式 不是现在
What the fuck man!?
你怎么了
Earlier you're ready to carry this girl on
your fucking shoulders to get help,
之前你准备扛着这女孩去寻找帮助
but now you won't
do it to help your friend.
但现在 你却不想帮你的朋友
What the fuck?!
怎么了
In fact, why aren't we
talking to the one person
事实上 我们干嘛不去问问那个
who might actually have
some answers here.
知道答案的人
Dan, what are you doing?
-I'm getting some answers!
丹 你在做什么
我在找答案
You can't do it like this, Dan.
Not like this!
你不能这么做 丹 不能这样
She knows something
and I'm going to find out!
她知道答案 而我要找出来
Listen to me. This
won't solve anything.
听我说 这不能解决问题
Its not this girls fault
that Doug is missing!
不是这个女孩的错 道格失踪了
Claire.
Get the fuck out of my way!
克莱尔 离我远点
Ted?
泰德
She has answers!
-Yeah!
她知道答案
是的
Maybe she does, but she's also been
through more than any of us know,
也许她知道 但她已经受不了了
and throwing her around the room right
now is not going to solve anything!
你这么做不是解决问题的办法
Move!
滚
No!
不
Ellie! Ellie!
艾莉 艾莉
No! Ted no!
不 泰德 不
Its ok.
没事的
-We have to get Doug!
我们要去找道格
No Ted!
-Its ok.
不 泰德
没事的
We have to get Doug.
我们要去找道格
No!
不
You can't go out there.
-No, please!
你不能出去
不 求你了
Help me get her inside.
帮我把她带进去
Ellie! Ellie!
You have to walk!
艾莉 艾莉 你要自己走
Come on. Come on.
We have to get you back inside!
起来 起来 我们要带你进去
She's got something in front of the door!
她用什么堵了门
Let us in you fucking cunt!
让我们进去 该死的混蛋
Dan.
丹
Go check the door on the porch.
去查看一下走廊上的门
Go!
去
Try to talk to her.
-Ok.
和她谈谈
好的
Honey?
甜心
Ok, listen to me.
We're here to help.
好吧 听我说 我们这儿需要帮助
Ok?
Please let us in.
好吗 让我们进去
[KNOCKING]
Honey?!
甜心
Doug!
道格
What are you doing?
-Nothing.
你在做什么
没事
How did you get in?
你怎么进去的
Claire got her to open up the door.
克莱尔让她开门的
Are you calm?
你还冷静吗
What are you talking about?
你在说什么
You can't go in unless
you're under control.
你不能进去 除非你能控制好自己
Look...we need some answers..and..and
this girl knows something..and
听着 我们需要答案 那女孩知道些事
Doug is our friend. I can't believe
you're choosing this girl over Doug!
道格是我们的朋友
我不相信你居然亲近她而超过道格
Lower-
轻点
She tried to lock us out of
the house, for Christ sakes!
天晓得她要把我们关在房子外
Lower your voice!
轻点声
She's finally not hysterical, do
you want to push her over the edge?
她好不容易没歇斯底里 你想刺激她吗
[WHISPERED] I don't give a fuck!
I just want to know what's going on...
我不想 我只想知道接下来怎么办
don't you?
-Yes of course I do!
你不想吗
是的 当然
We'll get our answers, don't worry about
that, but this girl on on the raggedy edge!
我们都想知道答案 但是这女孩在崩溃边缘
And the slightest thing can push her
to the point where she is useless.
现在她受不了一点点刺激
I want to do this because
I want to get Doug.
我这么做是为了找道格
But I don't want it to come to
"that", so calm the fuck down!
我不想前功尽弃 所以冷静一下
We need some answers-
我们需要答案
And we'll get them!
我们会得到的
Can you keep it together?
你能冷静了吗
Good.
好的
Let's go.
走吧
Wait...
等一下
Did she say anything?
她说过什么吗
Yeah, one thing...
是的
What's that?
是什么
I want to go home...
我想回家
So now what?
现在怎么样了
Is he ok?
-I'm right here you know.
他还好吗
我都在这儿了
Yeah, he's fine.
是的 他没事
Has she said anything else?
她还说了什么
[DAN]
We have to find out about Doug.
我们要找到道格
[TED]
He's right.
他说得对
We have to find out if she knows
anything about what happened to Doug.
我们要找 如果她知道道格发生了什么
She may be our only chance.
她也许是我们唯一的机会
What do you want me to do?
你想我做什么
I don't know. Try
to talk to her.
我不知道 试着和她沟通
You seem to be the only one who
can get in, even just a little.
你看上去是唯一可能打动她的人 只是可能
I've tried.
我会尽力
She won't tell me anything else.
她可能什么都不想和我说
I don't know what to do.
我不知道怎么办
Sweetie?
甜心
I need you to listen very closely here.
我需要你仔细听
Ok?
好吗
I know you've been through a lot, but
I need you to stay strong for me.
我知道你经历了很多 但我希望你坚强点
Can you do that for me?
你能为我这么做吗
I know its hard, baby.
我知道很难 宝贝
Its really hard, but I
need you to stay strong.
虽然难 但我希望你坚强点
Because we really need your help.
因为我们真的很需要你的帮助
Can you help us?
你能帮我们吗
Please?
拜托
What is your name, sweetheart?
你叫什么名字 甜心
Lisa...
丽萨
Hi Lisa.
嗨 丽萨
My name is Ellie.
我叫艾莉
Lisa, I need you to listen
very closely to me.
丽萨 我需要你仔细听我说
Ok?
好吗
I need to know exactly
what happened to you.
我想知道你发生了什么事
Where did you come from?
你从哪里来
I...
我
I was on the floor.
我在地板上
Floor?
地板
Ok.
Where was the floor?
好吧 哪里的地板
I don't know.
我不知道
I woke up and...
我醒来
Blood...
血
There was...
那儿
blood all around me.
我身边都是血
Stay with me, Lisa.
你和我在一起 丽萨
We're going to get
through this together.
我们一起渡过难关
Lisa?
Where was the blood?
丽萨 哪里的血
It was everywhere.
到处都是
My hands were wet...
我的手是湿的
I couldn't move at first,
离开时我动不了
but then...
但后来
my hands slipped through
something, and then I could.
我的手松开 可以动了
What happened then?
然后呢
My feet were tied.
我的脚被绑住了
I tried to untie my feet, but
my hands were so wet I couldn't.
我试着够我的脚 但我的手湿的 我做不到
Finally, I got them off, and I ran.
最后 我够到了 然后我就跑了
Where did you run from?
Was it a house?
你从哪里跑过来的 是不是一个房子
Yes.
是的
No.
不
A house in the trees.
是一个在树上的房子
Doug and I saw that house
when we were hiking.
道格和我徒步时 看到了那个房子
We were near it when
we were attacked.
当我们被袭击时 离它很近
A house in the trees?
在树上的房子
Do you know what she's talking about?
-I don't know.
你知道她在说什么吗
我不知道
It was dark.
I just followed her.
天很黑 我只是跟着她走
How did you get there?
你怎么去那儿的
I don't know.
我不知道
"He" brought me.
他带我去的
Who's "he"?
他是谁
He got my father, and my mother,
and then he came for me.
他带走我父亲 母亲 然后走向我
Who came for you, Lisa?
Who is it?
谁走向你 丽萨 谁
I don't know!
我不知道
Its ok, Lisa.
好吧 丽萨
Stay with me.
你和我在一起
Lisa, stay with me!
丽萨 你和我在一起
Where are your parents now?
你父母现在在哪儿
I don't know.
我不知道
He took them.
他抓走了他们
How did you know to come here?
你怎么知道来这儿的
How did you find this place? Did you
just find it while you were running?
你怎么发现这个地方的
你是跑的时候无意间发现的吗
How did you know to come here?
你怎么知道来这儿的
We were staying here when he took us.
他抓走我们的时候 我们住在这儿
Lisa, what was your dad's name?
丽萨 你爸爸叫什么
Robert Granger
罗伯特・格兰特
Fuck!
该死
Its fucking Bob!
是鲍勃
The same "Bob" that rented us the cabin?
是那个租房子给我们的鲍勃
Lisa, can you tell me anymore
about who took you?
丽萨 你能跟我说说那个抓你走的人吗
I don't know.
我不知道
He took you, and he tied you up?
他抓了你 然后绑了你吗
Yes.
是的
Could Doug still be alive?
那道格还会活着吗
Who's Doug?
-My husband.
谁是道格
我的丈夫
He was attacked by him.
Could he still be alive?
他袭击了他 他还活着吗
I don't know.
我不知道
If he took Doug, he
could still be alive.
如果他抓了道格 他可能还活着
We have to go after him, I
know where the place is.
我们要去找他 我知道那地方在哪儿
Ellie, we can't.
-We have to!
艾莉 我们不能
我们一定要去
He may still be alive, and if
there's a chance we have to go.
他可能还活着 只要有一线机会我们都要去
Ellie! I know, I want to get
Doug back too, but we can't go.
艾莉 我知道 我也想找道格回来 但我们不能去
Obviously whoever is doing this
knows the woods better than we do.
他显然比我们更熟悉这片森林
If we go out tonight we are never
going to come back.
我们今晚去 会一去不复返的
We have to wait until morning.
-What are you talking about?
我们要等到明天早上
你在说什么
Dan and I were almost there earlier!
丹和我之前几乎都到那儿了
We can't risk it! We have to get the
best odds, and that's to wait.
我们不能跑线 现在最好的办法就是等待
I can't, Ted!
我不能 泰德
I can't wait until morning, what if
he's dead by morning.
我等不到明早了 他可能会死
I can't wait knowing that Doug
may be lying on some bloody floor.
我等不了 道格可能正躺在那个都是血的地板
I just can't!
我不能
Dan? We have to go after him. You see
that right? We have to go after Doug!
丹 我们要去找他 你看过那儿的 我们要去找道格
Ellie. Ted is right.
艾莉 泰德是对的
We're no good at night.
We have to go after him tomorrow.
晚上太危险 我们必须明天再去找他
Fuck you both!
该死的你们
I'll go by myself, I don't need you.
I know where the place is!
我自己去 我不需要你们 我知道那地方在哪儿
Listen to me.
听我说
Listen to me!
If you wait until morning,
I promise you we will pack
如果你能等到明天早上
我保证我们会和你一起去
up every God damn weapon
we can find in here,
在这里找些趁手的武器
from a baseball bat to a ping pong paddle,
and we will not stop until we find Doug.
不管是棒球棒还是乒乓球拍都行
我们不会停止找寻道格的
I promise you that.
I promise you that!
我向你保证 我向你保证
Tomorrow? Who fucking cares about tomorrow?
How do you know he's not going to
明天 谁在乎明天 你怎么知道他不会
come in here in the middle of the night
and kill us all? What fucking tomorrow!?
在今夜来这里杀了我们所有人 见鬼的明天
We'll sleep in shifts to
make sure we're safe,
我们轮流睡来确保安全
and then come morning,
we will move on this fucker.
明天早上 我们会对这个混蛋采取行动的
Please.
求你了
Ellie, say ok.
艾莉 答应我
Say ok because you know where this place
is and we need you to get Doug back.
答应我 因为你知道那个地方
我们需要你来救道格回来
Please, help us get Doug back.
求你了 帮助我们救回道格
Please.
求你了
Please help us...
求你帮我们
Ok.
我答应
[WHISPER]
Doug!
道格
Shh, Ellie.
Its me.
艾莉 是我
Go back to sleep.
继续睡吧
How's it going?
怎么了
All is...quiet.
太安静了
That wasn't what I meant.
我不是问这个
I meant, how are you doing?
我是问 你怎么样了
Listen Ted...
听着 泰德
You already have two hysterical
women on your hands.
已经有两个歇斯底里的女人需要你照顾
The last thing you
need is a third.
可能有第三个了
What are you talking about?
你在说什么
I don't know how much more I can take.
我不知道我还能坚持多久
Everything happened so fast
with Ellie and Lisa,
艾莉和丽萨的事发生得太突然了
I didn't have a chance
to think about it.
我没机会好好想想
But I sure have
thought about this.
但我要好好想想
I don't know if I can do it.
我不知道我是否能负荷
Its too much.
发生了太多事情了
I don't know if I can put together the idea
of going to hunt for a man
who may have taken my friend hostage.
Or even worse...
How do you deal with it?
I don't know.
I mean, I guess I can't
really deal with that either.
I'm just trying not to.
I'm sure at some point I'm going to lose my
shit,but I just keep pushing that time off.
I'm just trying to get by.
It is what it-
Please don't say "It is what it is"
That is the biggest cop out in the
English language.
Its supposed to be so insightful,
but it just makes everything seem hollow.
Fair enough.
But I think you know what I mean.
I do.
Thanks Ted.
You're welcome.
All I know is that...
If I have to do anymore fucked
up shit this weekend,
I'm seriously going to reconsider
my camping plans for next year.
Aren't you scared?
Shitless.
I'm no hero.
I don't want to do this
anymore than you do.
But its the right thing to do.
I know.
You get any sleep?
No.
The chair upstairs is really uncomfortable.
All I got out of it was stiffness.
Well, why don't you go into a
bed and get some real sleep?
I'll stay up for a bit.
Alright.
Sounds like a deal.
If you don't mind though I'll use your bed.
It took Ellie forever to
get to sleep,
and I don't want to wake her up.
She really needs it right now.
No problem.
-Ok.
I should probably check on her
before I go to bed.
I'll do it.
Yeah?
-Yeah.
Just go to bed.
Ok.
What about you?
I'm tired but,
I think I would rather sleep
in the chair down here.
Ok.
Wake me up in a few hours?
Sure.
Ted?
Holy shit!
Dan, what's wrong?
Come on, fucker!
What?
He got Ellie!
Do you know where he is?
-I-
Do not fuck with me!
I know the trail that
Ellie was talking about.
If I take you back there,
can you find his hut?
I think so, maybe.
No fucking maybes!
Yes, or no!
Yes.
Let me tell you something.
It is fucking punt time.
I want you to get anything you can
use as a weapon.
We are going to find that son of a bitch
and get Ellie back. You got it?!
Yes.
Good.
Stay here, I'll be right back.
Do you know where that gun is?
I don't know.
It wasn't there, when you were here before?
No.
Shit.
Lisa.
I'm sorry about all this.
Its going to be a bit of a
hike up through that trail.
How's your ankle?
Its ok.
Let's just do what we have to do.
Let's go this way.
What's wrong? Is it your ankle?
That hurts but, no.
We're close.
This looks familiar.
Holy shit!
I can't go.
What?
I thought I could do this,
but I can't go in there.
You have to, there's no other way.
I'm sorry, but I can't. There is no way
with what I had to do to get out.
I can never
go back inside that place.
Think about what he did to you.
Your family!
I need you!
You don't need me.
I'll stay here and keep watch.
-What!
Look my ankle is on fire, I wouldn't be
able to make back up to that hut anyway.
So I'll stay here and keep a
look out in case he comes back.
And what if he's already in there?
Well, then I'm of no use
to you inside anyway.
Bring him out here.
Its not safe out here!
-I'll be fine.
I will signal you if he comes through here.
How?
I'll scream as loud as I can.
Then he's going to come right after you.
Well, at the very least,
it will take his attention
away from the hut and
you can surprise him.
Promise me Ted, you'll
come running if I scream.
I promise...
but I don't like this idea.
Its all I have.
This is insane!
Hold on, I'll be right back.
[WHISPER]
Ellie.
Ellie!
Ok, he's not there and I see Ellie.
Is she alive?
I think so, but she's unconscious.
Get out of sight, and only scream
if he is definitely going in.
Here take these.
-What?
I can't carry her out with these.
Scream loud.
You'll come?
I'll come.
Oh shit!
Shit!
Nope.